woisio.com 2015-11-14

# woisio-privacy-policy

**Last updated: February 5th, 2015.**

The use of the Woisio website(s), application(s), software, services and products (collectively, the “Woisio Service” or “Service”) are subject to this Privacy Policy including any amendments or updates hereto in addition to the Woisio Terms & Conditions. 

We are providing this privacy policy to inform you of our practices with respect to how we collect and use your personally identifiable information while you are using the Woisio Service.

By using the Woisio Service you agree to the collection and use of your personal information for the purposes described below. Woisio reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time without notice, and it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy for any changes. Your use of the Woisio Service following any amendment of this Privacy Policy will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised terms.

If you are under the age of 13, you are not eligible to use the Woisio Service, and we ask you not to submit any personal information to us.

Please note that any video, audio, image, or other content posted to the Woisio Service from your account becomes published content (even before they air) and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.

Click [here](mailto:cancel-account@woisio.com?subject=Delete%20my%20account "Send email to cancel-account@woisio.com from your registered e-mail.") to cancel your account. We will delete all the personally identifiable information and any non-aired content from our servers along with your account.

###  1\. INFORMATION COLLECTED

We do collect personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, username, email address, date of birth, phone number/id, location, preferences, facebook and/or twitter usernames etc when you voluntarily provide it by registering with us or using the Woisio Service.

We also do collect many non personally identifiable data about users of the Woisio Service (e.g., IP address, current location, browser type, mobile platform, pages accessed, duration of visit, use of a particular features or offers, clicks and other analytical information etc.) automatically whether or not you are a registered user. 

In order to collect this data and enhance your experience through personalization (help authenticate your identity; remember preferences and other information you have provided before; present personalized recommendations, offerings and advertisements; help measure the effectiveness of these and other communications) Woisio may utilize automated tools and files such as cookies (might be disabled through your browser), web beacons or similar technologies. These may reside on our servers or on your computer or device. If you restrict our ability to use automated tools and files, your ability to access and use all or part of the Woisio Service may be limited or disabled completely.

We may use local shared objects (LSOs), commonly called Flash cookies, to store your preferences or serve content based on yours / friends’ content history. Third party service providers like our advertisers may also use LSOs to collect and store information. Your browser’s cookie management settings/tools will have no effect on LSOs. To learn how to effectively manage LSOs please click [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html "Learn how to effectively manage LSOs"). If you disable LSOs, you won't have access to some features and some of our services will not function properly.

###  2\. USE OF INFORMATION

Main use of the non personally identifiable information is to continuously improve the Woisio Service. By looking at the statistics derived from the information we collected, we can see what is working, what is not and act on it.

Woisio uses your personally identifiable information primarily to provide you with the services (as personalized as possible) on the Woisio Service. The information is also used to verify your authority to access the Woisio Service, post content, write comments, vote, bid for / buy air times, upload / edit / delete / air content and to contact you when reasonably necessary. 

Woisio may also use any information you have provided as reasonably necessary to administer or provide customer support for the Woisio Service, and to provide you with periodic printed or e-mail communications about new products and services, discounts, special promotions or upcoming events. You may opt-out of receiving some or all optional communications (when and if they exist) by updating your profile on the Woisio Service. (You can not opt-out of some very important communications like reset password e-mails, verification e-mails etc.) 

Also, your full name and email address may be used when you use the Woisio Service to send a message or an invitation to another user. Additionally, we use your email address to contact you on behalf of other friends on the site (such as when another user sends you a message or invites you to join a conversation).

Woisio may use your facebook and/or twitter username and required account information to post (shares, likes, check ins, etc) on your behalf (if you authorize Woisio to do so)

Woisio may use your personally identifiable information to personalize the advertisements and promoted contents or to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers.

Woisio may also use your personally identifiable information to enter you into any sweepstakes, giveaway or contest conducted by Woisio (may be through business partners or third parties on behalf of Woisio). However; if you win (pending your acceptance of the Official Rules), none of your information will be published (name, username, location etc.) until you agree to the Official Rules of that specific sweepstakes, giveaway or contest. If you choose not to agree to the Official Rules of that specific promotion; Woisio will select a new winner per Official Rules and your information will not be published with this regard.

###  3\. INFORMATION DISCLOSURE

You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g. name, e-mail address) via comments, forums, postings, profiles or other areas of the Woisio Service, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in your communication, can be collected, correlated and used by third parties. Please do not post any personal information on the Woisio Service or in other areas that you expect to keep private.

Woisio will disclose your personally identifiable information as it believes is reasonably necessary to comply with law, regulation or other governmental authority or to prevent harm to yourself or others.

Woisio may display your profile information, location, comments, current watched content, list of favorite/followed/selected/grouped stages, check ins, badges etc while posting on your behalf (if you authorize Woisio to do so) with your facebook or twitter account. 

Woisio may also work with or contract third parties related to various design and operations aspects of the Woisio Service. We may for example use a third party to process payments, maintain support functionality, serve advertisements etc. In these cases, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to prevent such third parties from disclosing your personal information, except for the purpose of providing the services in question. 

Finally, Woisio may transfer personally identifiable information in the event of a transfer of ownership of Woisio or any of its websites or products, in which case the information could become subject to a different privacy policy.

**California Privacy Policy**

Woisio will not share your personal information for direct marketing purposes without prior consent from you. If you have previously consented but no longer wish your information to be shared please let us know by sending an e-mail to [privacy@woisio.com](mailto:privacy@woisio.com "Send email to privacy@woisio.com") for the fastest possible response.

You can fax your request to +1 (877) 778-3223

You can also send your request to

Privacy Agent  
Woisio  
2997 East Cobb Pkwy #724256  
Atlanta, GA 31139

**Links**

Woisio may provide links to third party websites or referrals to third parties’ products or services. If you choose to visit a third party’s website or use its products or services, please be aware that the third party’s privacy policy will govern your activities and any information you disclose while interacting with the third party.

###  4\. ADVERTISING

Woisio allows third party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit. They may use non personally identifiable information (click stream information, browser type, mobile platform, time and date, location, type of advertisements engaged with, etc.) during your visits to this site and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third-party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising (from the participating advertisers), you can click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp "Learn more about this behavioral advertising practice") or visit the companies by clicking on the adchoices icon on the banners where available.

Woisio uses Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online (Click [here](http://support.google.com/analytics/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=2611268&topic=2611283&ctx=topic "Learn more about remarketing") to learn more). Third-party vendors, including Google, shows Woisio’s ads on sites across the internet. Woisio and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone's past visits to Woisio website.

Woisio uses Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting to better understand the demographic and interest breakdown of the Woisio visitors in order to add/remove relevant/irrelevant stages (channels) to Woisio Lineup, and improve the content alignment with existing stages (channels). Woisio also uses this insight to better align ads with stages (channels). 

If you would like to opt-out of receiving advertising like this from Google, or change any of the demographic or interest information about you; you can manage these settings by visiting the [Google Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/ "Google Ads Settings"). Also, Google recommends installing the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/ "Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on").

Woisio will not facilitate the merging of personally-identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information previously collected from Display Advertising features that is based on the DoubleClick cookie unless we have robust notice of, and your prior affirmative (i.e., opt-in) consent to, that merger.

We may display interest-based ads to you when you are using Facebook through a tool offered by Facebook called the Custom Audience Tool. This tool allows us to personalize our ads based on your browsing experience with us. We do not share any of your personal information with Facebook. The tool lets Woisio convert your email address to a unique number that Facebook uses to match to unique numbers Facebook generates from email addresses of its users. You may opt-out of Facebook Custom Audience ads from Woisio by clicking [here](http://woisio.com/opt-out/facebook "Opt-Out Facebook")

###  5\. DATA SECURITY

Woisio attaches great importance to the security of your data, and takes all appropriate steps to limit the risk that it may be lost, damaged or misused. However since any personally identifiable information you submit to Woisio is purely voluntary and should not be of a particularly sensitive nature we do not use special encryption methods. 

Woisio user accounts are protected by user created passwords. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and personal information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and signing off after use. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time.

All our personnel that have access to, and are associated with the processing of your personally identifiable information are obligated to respect the confidentiality of the information.

Woisio is not a platform for safekeeping your content. We do not accept any liability if content is lost, wrongfully deleted, or no longer accessible. Only purpose of Woisio storing your content is to air it through purchased timeslots.

###  6\. MODIFICATION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATON

If you would like us to delete the personally identifiable information (all or some parts of it) you have submitted, or make changes to it that can’t be done through the user interface (or if you don’t know how to do it through the user interface) please send an e-mail to [privacy@woisio.com](mailto:privacy@woisio.com "Send email to privacy@woisio.com") with your request.

Please note that deletion of your personally identifiable information from Woisio’s database will not prevent Woisio from using gathered anonymous information.

###  7\. SPECIAL NOTE TO CHILDREN UNDER 13 AND THEIR PARENTS / LEGAL GUARDIANS

If you are under the age of 13, you are not eligible to use the Woisio Service, and we ask you not to submit any personal information to us. 

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information relating to children under the age of 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior parental consent, we will take steps to promptly delete such information. By providing your personal information to Woisio, you represent that you are 13 years of age or older.

If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under the age of 13, and that child has somehow registered with Woisio, please send an e-mail to [privacy@woisio.com](mailto:privacy@woisio.com "Send email to privacy@woisio.com") for instructions on how to cancel your child's registration. 

In the e-mail, please provide your full name and address, your child's full name and address, your relationship to the child, your daytime and evening telephone numbers, your e-mail address and a signed statement that you are the child's parent or legal guardian. Woisio will use this information only to verify that you are the child's parent or legal guardian and for no other purpose.

###  8\. NON-US USERS

Woisio Service is hosted in the United States. If you are using the Woisio Service from any other location other than the US with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from the US law; please note that by providing your personal data you consent to the use of your personal data for the purposes identified above in accordance with this Privacy Policy, and the transfer of your personal data to the United States.

###  9\. LEGAL NOTICES

Woisio does not guarantee error free performance under this Privacy Policy. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with it. We welcome your feedback regarding any privacy concerns that you may have, including how we can improve this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy is subject to the terms in Woisio Terms & Conditions, available for review at here. Our Terms & Conditions take precedence over any conflicting provision in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices exercised by other providers of products or services, advertisers or other web sites, or companies / people that Woisio does not own or control, or does not employ or manage.

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please feel free to contact us by sending an e-mail to [privacy@woisio.com](mailto:privacy@woisio.com "Send email to privacy@woisio.com") for the fastest possible response.

You can contact us via fax to +1 (877) 778-3223

You can also send us a mail to:

Privacy Agent  
Woisio  
2997 East Cobb Pkwy #724256  
Atlanta, GA 31139
